

Profile

As a Frontend Developer I love to solve problems, learn new things and have a great passion for design and creating an amazing user experience. In my career history I have strengthened my ability to always find a solution for every problem and think outside of the box. As an Engineer I know how to deal with stressful situation and always remain calm. My background in sales as well as my emotional intelligence make me a great team player. My whole life I have been learning things on my own alongside great teachers and I can't wait to truly begin this journey as a Frontend Web Developer.

Employment History

Product Developement Software, IB&T Software Company, Hamburg

2018 - 2019

Quality assurance of new software features. I was testing new functionalities and reported bugs and recommendations to the developers. With my help we were able to ship one of the latest innovations on the engineering software market.

Sales Consultant, Daikin Airconditioning, München

2019 - 2020

Acquiring new customers and projects and creating concepts for air conditioning systems for large projects. I introduced our team to a new way to analyze the relationships to our customers based on a visual model of important attributes, that lead to an increase in customers and sales

Traffic Light Engineer, City of Hamburg

FEBRUARY 2020 - JULY 2022

As a Infrastructural Engineer, it was my response to analyze intersections and write the program of new traffic light software. I achieved to become the manager of the city's biggest hardware & software update with over 100 intersections being affected and optimized the schedule so we were able to shorten the estimated end of the project by about 20%.

Education

MS, Hafencity Universität Hamburg

2018 - 2020

Infrastructural Engineering

BS, Hafencity Universität Hamburg

2011 - 2017

Civil Engineering

Courses

CS50 Introduction to Computer Science, University of Harvard

JULY 2021 - DECEMBER 2021

build and deploy an NFT collection with DAO interface, _buildspace

2022 - 2022

Details

Hamburg Germany +49 176 47838232

cophi.dev@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

Portfolio

Skills

React

JavaScript

HTML5

CSS

Git

Figma

Hobbies

I love to be around the nature with my two daughters and dog, to work out and travel around Europe. I constantly need to learn new skills and just love the challenge and that moment of finally getting it, like playing guitar, solving a rubik's cube

Languages

German

English